## Naim Syed . Jarvis Consulting

I am a Business Systems Analyst at Jarvis Consulting with a strong interest in data analytics and automation. I have a bachelor's in accounting from Toronto Metropolitan University and a certificate in Data Science from Lighthouse Labs. I have four years of experience working in the pension and benefits industry where I have led projects to automate business processes by integrating ERP systems and building custom RPA solutions. I also supported decision-making in policy development by analyzing financial. During my free time, I enjoy playing recreational sports and captaining a Sunday league basketball team.

#### Skills

Proficient: Python, Linux/Bash, RDBMS/SQL, Workday/ERP's, Agile/Scrum

Competent: PowerBI/Tableau, Project Management, Financial Analysis, Excel (Pivot Tables), Docker, Git

Familiar: Java, HTML/CSS, Google Cloud Platform, Jira/Confluence, UIPath (RPA), Machine Learning

## **Jarvis Projects**

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis data eng NaimSyed

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Developed a monitoring agent that retrieves hardware specifications and usage data for Linux machines to support resource planning. Collected data using Linux shell scripts utilizing regex and bash commands to filter and parse through results. Stored data by leveraging a PostgreSQL database in a docker container. Automated scripts using cron commands to provide real-time data.

### **Highlighted Projects**

**UIPath Invoice Processor**: Developed a custom RPA solution using UIPath to automatically generate cost center breakdowns to allocate employee benefit expense invoices. I collaborated with cross-functional teams using agile to manage timelines across the planning, development, and testing phases. The final product helped result in a reduction in manual administration time by 70%.

TMU Group RRSP Restructuring Project: Led a project to improve employee participation in the Group RRSP valued at >\$17 million. I analyzed data on 50+ funds offered by TMU and established a risk profile based on employee demographics and relevant contribution trends. I then finalized 20 top-performing funds to recommend and presented my findings to key stakeholders with a positive reception and moved forward with implementation.

#### **Professional Experiences**

Business Systems Analyst, Jarvis (September 2024 - present): Worked on various projects using relevant technologies such as Linux/Bash, SQL, Java, Data Analytics with Python, and Docker. I collaborated with team members using Agile to achieve project goals.

Analyst, Payroll and Benefits Operations, CPP Investments (July 2021 - June 2023): Collaborated with cross-functional departments to lead Workday system enhancement projects including vendor system integrations, implementing self-service benefit administration, automated benefit allowance notifications, and expense report data integrity controls. Contributed to policy development by analyzing pension and benefits data and effectively communicating recommendations to stakeholders.

Pension and Benefits Administrator, Toronto Metropolitan University (May 2019 - June 2021): Managed pension and benefits administration for over 1000 employees. Led initiatives to improve employee partication in Group RRSP programs by analyzing contribution data. Managed tracking and distribution of retirement packages for over 100 retirees for an incentive program, ensuring smooth retirement transitions. Developed internal reports to streamline pension buyback calculations.

#### Education

Toronto Metropolitan University (2015 - 2020), Bachelor of Commerce - Accounting Major, Ted Rogers School of Management

# Miscellaneous

- Lighthouse Labs Diploma in Data Science (2024)
- Tutor
- Guitar Player
- Recreational Basketball/Soccer Player